Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Records SC0112
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Cataloging
  - Building Plans - Research Library, 1967-1976 (Box 252, Folder 22)
  - Building Services - Alarms, 1980-1981 (Box 252, Folder 23)
  - Building Services - Custodial, 1976-1981 (Box 252, Folder 24)
  - Building Services - Earthquake Man, 1981 (Box 252, Folder 25)
  - Building Services - Emergency Exits, 1978-1980 (Box 252, Folder 26)
  - Building Services - Fumigation, 1977-1981 (Box 252, Folder 27)
  - Building Services - Keys, 1976-1981 (Box 252, Folder 28)
  - Building Services - Photocopy (Box 252, Folder 29)
  - Building Services - Security, 1974-1981 (Box 252, Folder 30)
  - Building Services - Telephones, 1964-1981 (Box 252, Folder 31)
  - Building Services - Typewriters, 1973-1981 (Box 252, Folder 32)
  - Building Services - Ventilation, 1965-1981 (Box 252, Folder 33)
  - Business Services, 1970-1979 (Box 252, Folder 34)
  - California Library Association, 1974-1979 (Box 252, Folder 35)
  - Calif. Union Catalog, Sacramento, 1975-1981 (Box 252, Folder 36)
  - Call Number Notation, 1963-1980 (Box 252, Folder 37)
  - Cameras, 1970-1981 (Box 252, Folder 38)
  - Card Catalog, 1970-1975 (Box 252, Folder 39)
  - Card Catalog Cabinets, 1977-1981 (Box 252, Folder 40)
  - Card Catalogs - Closing of, 1968-1979 (Box 252, Folder 41)
  - Catalog Card Loss, 1979-1981 (Box 252, Folder 42)
  - Catalog Card Production, 1971-1972 (Box 252, Folder 43)
  - Catalog Cards, 1970-1979 (Box 252, Folder 44)
  - Catalog Cards - Replacement Cards, 1969-1981 (Box 252, Folder 45)
  - Catalog Data Slips, 1977 (Box 252, Folder 46)
  - Catalog Department File, 1974-1981 (Box 252, Folder 48)
  - Catalog Department - Goals amp; Objectives, 1970-1981 (Box 252, Folder 49)
  - Catalog Department Meetings, 1970-1981 (Box 252, Folder 50)
  - Catalog Department Organization, 1972-1981 (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - Catalog Dept. - Unit Heads Meeting, 1980-1981 (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - Catalog Expansion, 1968-1975 (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - Catalog Manual (Typing Section), 1971 (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - Cataloging Assignments, 1970-1981 (Box 253, Folder 6)
  - Cataloging Backlog, 1979-1981 (Box 253, Folder 7)
  - Cataloging Category - (CC) Field, 1981 (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - Cataloging Problems, 1980 (Box 253, Folder 9)
  - Cataloging Standards, 1978-1981 (Box 253, Folder 10)
  - CDS (Cataloging Distribution Service), 1979-1981 (Box 253, Folder 11)
  - Central Circulation Department, 197501980 (Box 253, Folder 12)
  - CETA, 1978-1979 (Box 253, Folder 13)
  - Chemical Abstractsl Access Update Prog., 1970 (Box 253, Folder 14)
  - Chemical Engineering Library, 1966-1977 (Box 253, Folder 15)
  - Chinese Cooperative Cataloging, 1972-1974 (Box 253, Folder 16)
  - CIN (Cooperatice Information Network), 1977-1979 (Box 253, Folder 17)
  - CIP (Cataloging in Publication), 1971-1979 (Box 253, Folder 18)
  - CLAN, 1973 (Box 253, Folder 19)
  - CLASS, 1975-1979 (Box 253, Folder 20)
  - Classics Library, 1972-1981 (Box 253, Folder 21)
  - Classification (Bibliographic), 1974-1979 (Box 253, Folder 22)
  - Closing The Catalog Institute (LITA), 1979 (Box 253, Folder 23)
  - COGR, 1977 (Box 253, Folder 24)
  - Collection Development Council, 1977-1979 (Box 253, Folder 25)
  - Collection Development Program, 1979 (Box 253, Folder 26)
  - CDP - Germanic, 1970-1979 (Box 253, Folder 27)
  - CDP - Latin America, 1970-1980 (Box 253, Folder 28)
  - CDP - Romance, 1975-1979 (Box 253, Folder 29)
  - Columbia University, 1977-1980 (Box 253, Folder 30)
  - COMARC, 1977-1978 (Box 253, Folder 31)
  - Communication, 1976-1981 (Box 253, Folder 32)
  - Comparable Rewards, 1977-1978 (Box 253, Folder 33)
  - Compound Surmanes, 1973-1974 (Box 253, Folder 34)
  - Computer Data Tapes, 1972-1979 (Box 253, Folder 35)
  - Conference Card, 1970-1981 (Box 253, Folder 36)
  - Congresses - Cataloging of 1981 (Box 253, Folder 37)
  - Conservation and Preservation to 1981, 1977-1981 (Box 253, Folder 38)
  - Continuation Cards, 1974-1975 (Box 253, Folder 39)
  - Copy Cataloging, 1979-1982 (Box 253, Folder 40)
  - Copy Cataloging Unit, 1976-1981 (Box 253, Folder 41)
  - Cornell University, 1972-1979 (Box 253, Folder 42)
  - Council on Library Resources, 1971-1982 (Box 253, Folder 43)
  - CPPC, 1981 (Box 253, Folder 44)
  - CPPC, 1980 (Box 253, Folder 45)
  - CPPC, 1979 (Box 253, Folder 46)
  - CPPC, 1978 (Box 253, Folder 47)
  - CPPC, 1977 (Box 253, Folder 48)
  - CPPC, 1976 (Box 253, Folder 49)
- Acquisitions
  - Current Library Systems Study - Part 2 of 2, 1970 Feb (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Procedure for Running Off Computer-Produced spine labels (number 3) (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Current Library Systems Study- Part 1 of 2, 1970 Feb (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Report of the Commission on Librarianships at Stanford, 1975 Mar (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Reserves - Anthro-Greek, Fall 1977 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Hansen Chronological File, July-December 1979 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Hansen Chronological File, January-June 1979 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Hansen Chronological File, 1978 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Hansen Chronological File, January-June 1977 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Hansen Chronological File, June-December 1977 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Send for Copies (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Acquisition System Design, 1968 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Ballots: System Development Book, 1970 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Status Report on Ballots, 1978 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - The Libraries of Stanford University: 1990 and Beyond (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Ballots Liason, 1978 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Ballots Acquisitions (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Fiche-Film Conversion (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Library Administration Regulations, 1976 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Proc/Rec (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Searching Pro. (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - O.P. Orders (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Ordering Procedure, 1966-1968 (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - Order, 1976-1977 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Order, 1978 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence #3 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Supervisory Orientation Program, 1978 May (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - RLIN (Box 208, Folder 3)
- Serials
- Stanford University Librarians Assembly (SULA)
  - SULA, 1977-1978 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - SULA Executive Board meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - SULA Professional Concerns Committee, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - SULA Professional Concerns Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - SULA membership meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - SULA accounts (bank statements), 1969-1977 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - SULA Executive Board meetings, 1979-1980 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - SULA Professional Concerns Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - SULA News, 1979-1980 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - SULA Program Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Academic Council Committee on Libraries, 1980-1981 (Box 112a, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board, 1980-1981 (Box 112a, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board, 1980-1981 (Box 112a, Folder 3)
  - Membership, 1980 (Box 112a, Folder 4)
  - Professional Concerns Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 112a, Folder 5)
  - Program Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 112a, Folder 6)
  - University Library Council, 1980-1981 (Box 112a, Folder 7)
  - SULA, 1980-1981 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - SULA, 1981-1982 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - SULA, 1982-1983 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - SULA, 1983-1984 (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - ACCL, 1981-1982 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - ACCL, 1982-1983 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board, 1981-1982 (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board, 1982-1983 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Membership Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Membership Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Membership Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Professional Concerns Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 224, Folder 8)
  - Professional Concerns Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 224, Folder 9)
  - Program Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 224, Folder 10)
  - Program Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 224, Folder 11)
  - SULA News, 1981-1982 (Box 224, Folder 12)
  - SULA News, 198201983 (Box 224, Folder 13)
  - Task Force (Box 224, Folder 14)
  - University Library Council (Box 224, Folder 15)
  - University Library Council (Box 224, Folder 16)
- Associates
  - Budget and Funds Statement, 9/77-8/78 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - General, 1978-1980 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Budget and Funds Statement, 9/78-8/79 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Budget and Funds Statement, 9/79-8/80 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Budget and Funds Statement, 9/80-8/81 (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Budget and Funds Statement, 9/81-8/82 (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - Restricted NXA605, 9/82-8/83 (Box 221, Folder 7)
  - Hum. Endowment NKE305, 9/82-8/83 (Box 221, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Expenditures, 29952 (Box 221, Folder 9)
  - Operations NXA605, 9/82-8/83 (Box 221, Folder 10)
  - ASL Endowed Book Fund in the Humanities 3NRB205 (Box 221, Folder 11)
  - Misc. Expenditures, 9/77-12/81 (Box 221, Folder 12)
  - Membership Brochure (Box 221, Folder 13)
  - Renewal Correspondence, 1975-August 1977 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Membership Solicitation, 1975-August 1977 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Acquisitions, 1975-1977 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors and Advisory Council, 1973-1977 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1973-August 1977 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Budget & Funds Statements, 1973-August 1977 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Expenditures, 1975-August 1977 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Imprint - General Vols. I-III, 1975-1977 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Imprint - Vols. I-III, 1975-1977 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Associates records, Accession ARCH-1996-242
    - 10th anniversary/5 millionth book, 30598 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - English Dept./Winters, 30752 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - San Diego Trip, April 6-8, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Annual meetinglMusic Lib. Program, 30786 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Prof. Donald Harper "Written on Bamboo and Silk", 30806 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Delmar Davis, 30814 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Steinbeck Country Trip, 30803 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Picnic and Book Auction, 30843 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Auction, 29743 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Japan Trip, 30590 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Book collecting lectures, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Book collecting lectures, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Book collecting lectures, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Book fair, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Bylaws, historical through 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors, 1978-1982/83 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Advisory Council, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, 1974-1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Roper Public Opinion Research Center, Accession ARCH-1983-123, 1991-045
- Administrative Services, Accession ARCH-1988-045
  - Accounting and Financial Information (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Automated Budget (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Automation, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Budget (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Budgetary Planning Group, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Budget Protocols (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - DAP Program, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Capital Equipment (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Library Materials (Book Fund) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Salary Savings (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Sponsored Projects Office (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - HEA II-C (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Staff Planning (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chart of Accounts (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Circulation Automation (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - DIASG (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Circulation System Work Group (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Staff Development (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Graphics and Publications (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Library Bulletin (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Policy & Procedures Manuals (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Public Relations (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Building Services - General (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Laser Printing (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Mail/Messenger and Supplies (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Photocopy (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Procurement (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Building Projects - General; Priorities, Auxiliary Library (SAL); Bender Room; Commisarry; Disaster Plan; Facilities Plan; Hazards Survey; Heating, Ventilation, and Air Conditioning (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Meyer Library (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Photocopy Task Force (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Portal Security Checkpoint (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Robinson Room (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Rotunda Security (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Space (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Sotrage (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Technical Service Renovation (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Tiered Stacks (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Systems Office - General; AEP; AIS; Automation Budget; Automation Plan; ITS; ITS Communications; SUNet; Micro Training; RLIN Budget (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Circulation Automation (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Sponsored Projects Office (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Controller's Office (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - SUNet (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - On-Line Catalong - Socrates (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - FY86 Socrates Costs (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University/Berkeley Cooperative Programs (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - SUL Organization (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - RLG Consolidated Budget, 1984-1985 and 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - RLIN (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - RLG (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - NRLF (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Directors' Office Automation (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - CLR Economics Seminar (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Retrospective Conversion (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Georg Olms Verlag - Catalog Microfilm (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Conservation (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Collection Development Program (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Development Office (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chicano (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Special Collections (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Blackwell North American (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Meyer Library (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Public Services (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Access Services (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Technical Information Services (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Branch Libraries: General (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Music Library (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Science Library (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Government Documents (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Close Card Catalog (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Catalog (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Binding & Finishing (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - The Libraries of Stanford University: 1900 and Beyond, 29312 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Report on the Commission on Librarianship at Stanford, 27454 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Library Materials Budgeting in Twelve Private University Libraries, 28734 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Green Library Additional Facility Requirements, 28550 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - The Economics of Book Catalog Production, 23498 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - The New University Library, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Stanford University Libraries Report on Administrative Reorganization, 27485 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - UCB-Stanford Research Library Cooperative Program, 27973 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Task Force on Library Orientation and Bibliographic Instruction - Preliminary Report, 28734 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - The Past and Likely Future of 58 Research Libraries, 1951-1980: A Statistical Study of Growth and Change, 1963-1964, 1964-1965; 1965-1966; 1968-1969; 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University Archives: A Guide to Archival and Manuscript Collections (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Toward the Library of the 21st century (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Planning for a Nationwide System of Library statistics (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Academic Research Libraries: A Study of Growth, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Library Statistics of Colleges and Universities, 1959-60 (Part 1); 1961-62 (Parts 1 and 2); 1962-63 (Institutional Data); 1965-66 (Institutional Data); Fall, 1968; Fall, 1969 (Analytical Report), Fall, 1971., 1959-1971 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - College and University Library statistics, 1957-1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - California Library Statistics and Directory, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Analytical Planning for University Libraries (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Development of a Long-Range Strategic Plan for a University Library: The Cornell Experience (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - A Model Budget Analysis System for Libraries, 25628 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - The Study of Education at stanford: Report University, Volumes II through VIII (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - New Directions for Higher Education: Priorities for Academic Librarians (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - The study of Education at Stanford - Report to the University: The Study and Its Purposes (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - New Directions for Higher Education: Making the Budget Process Work (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Academic Libraries: The Changing Knowledge Colleges and Universities, Report 8 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - The University Library: Analysis and Proposals, 26846 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Report on the Commission on Librarianship at Stanford, 27454 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - A Cost Analysis and Utilization Study System of the Stanford University Library System, 23774 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Summary of a Feasibility study on the Participation of Four colleges and Universities in a Stanford University Library Automation Network, 26238 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Project for Evaluating the Benefits from University Libraries, Final Report, 25477 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Return on Investment for Library Automation, 27485 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Library Technology Reports, May/June 1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Preliminary Cost Analysis of Selected Library Functions at Stanford university, Volumes I through III, 25477 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Survey of Library Material Expenditures at Stanford University Libraries, 28034 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Campaign for Stanford - The Univeristy Progress Fund: Stanford Unviersity (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Campaign for Stanford - The Research Development Fund: Stanford Unviersity (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - The Campaign for Stanford - The New University Library Stanford University (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Managin Under Austerity, Summary Proceedings (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Preliminary Findings and Recommendations on the Financial review of the Stanford Library, 25020 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Criteria for Evaluating the Effectiveness of Library Operations and Services - Phase III: Recommended Criteria and Methods for Their Utilization, 25204 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - A Systems Analysis of the Library and Information Science Statistical Data System: The Research Investigation, Part I and PartII, 25720 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - More for Less - Academic Planning with Faculty without New Dollars, 27120 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Data Collection and Cost Modeling for Library Circulation Systems, 25873 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - A Cost Analysis and Utilization Study of the Stanford University Library System, 23774 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Meyer Library
  - Meyer Library records, Accession ARCH-1988-066
  - Meyer Library records, Accession ARCH-2001-064
  - Meyer Library records, Accession ARCH-2001-168
- Government Documents
  - Jonsson Library of Government Documents annual reports, 1954-1987; Accession ARCH-1988-089
  - Jonsson Library of Government Documents seminar records, Accession ARCH-1989-053
  - Organization of American States Classification Manual, 1970 Jan; Accession ARCH-2015-027 (Box 1)
- Systems Office records, 1971-1980; Accession ARCH-1989-073
- Acquisitions, Accession ARCH-1989-134
  - Acquisitions, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Acquisitions, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Acquisitions, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Acquisitions, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Acquisitions, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - BAP - Periodaes [?], 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bibliographies (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Theatre Collection--History and Housing (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Reserve Book List Forms (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - TLA/ALA (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Stark Index Pub1. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Simonson Collection (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco Players Guild (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lurie proposal (Box 2, Folder envelope)
  - Lurie Press Books (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Louis R. Lurie Collection (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - IBM - Kennedy Center (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Guide to Theatre Collection (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Drama Dept. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Delmen Daves Collection (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-1992-129
- Access Services
  - Access Services records, Accession ARCH-1993-010
  - Access Services records, Accession ARCH-2007-280
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2000-172
- Germanic curator's files, Accession ARCH-2000-270
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2002-083
- Braun Music Library records, Accession ARCH-2002-084
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2003-091
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2002-221
  - AAHE, 1994 (Box 1)
  - AA Positions (Box 1)
  - AAU (Box 1)
  - Academic Council Committee of the 34th Senate (Box 1)
  - Academic Council Committee on Info. Technology (Box 1)
  - Academic Information Infrastructure Planning (Box 1)
  - Academic Staff (Box 1)
  - Academic Software Computing (Box 1)
  - Access to Information Infrastructure Plan (Box 1)
  - Access Services (Box 1)
  - Access Services (Box 1)
  - Access Services (Box 1)
  - ACCL (Box 1)
  - Action Plans for Change (APC) (Box 2)
  - Acquisitions (Box 1)
  - 3-Year Plan (Box 1)
  - Access to Information Group (Box 1)
  - Access Survey of Libraries and Computers at Stanford (Box 1)
  - Accreditation Self Study (Box 1)
  - Acquisition Dept. (Box 1)
  - Acquisitions/Serials (Box 1)
  - Acquisitions/Serials (Box 1)
  - Acqusitions (Box 1)
  - Acquisitions (Box 1)
  - Acquisitions/Serials Department (Box 1)
  - Acquisitions/Serials (Box 1)
  - Academic Staff (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services (Box 2)
  - Advising Students (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council (Box 2)
  - AES's Infrastructure (Box 2)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 2)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 2)
  - Affimative Action (Box 2)
  - AIR Amortization (Box 2)
  - Allan, Bill (Box 2)
  - Altman, Russ (Box 2)
  - American Antiquarian Society (Box 2)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 2)
  - American Heritage (Box 2)
  - American West (Box 2)
  - Annual Report (Box 2)
  - Annual Report (Box 2)
  - Annual Report (Box 2)
  - Annual Report (Box 2)
  - Annual Report (Box 2)
  - Annual report (Box 2)
  - Action Plan for Change-Libraries (Box 2)
  - Alan Nichols (Box 2)
  - Al Tallone, Alberto (Box 2)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 2)
  - Annual Report (Box 3)
  - Annual Report (Box 3)
  - Annual Reports (Box 3)
  - Annual Review (Box 3)
  - Annual Statistics (Box 3)
  - Anthropology Department (Box 3)
  - Anti-Management (Box 3)
  - Apple (Box 3)
  - APS Workshop (Box 3)
  - ARL (Box 3)
  - ARL (Box 3)
  - ARL (Box 3)
  - ARL (Box 3)
  - ARL (Box 3)
  - ARL (Box 3)
  - ANSI (Box 3)
  - Annual Statistics (Box 3)
  - Approval Plan Reviews (Box 3)
  - Archives and Manuscripts Preservation Project (Box 3)
  - ARL (Box 3)
  - ARL (Box 3)
  - Ansel Adams Fund (Box 3)
  - Apple, Martin (Box 3)
  - ARL (Box 4)
  - ARL (Box 4)
  - Arms Control Center Library (Box 4)
  - Art and Architecture Department (Box 4)
  - Art Library (Box 4)
  - ASBMB/DBC-ACS (Box 4)
  - ASD Redesign (Box 4)
  - Asia Foundation Intern (Box 4)
  - Associated Audio Archives (Box 4)
  - ASUL (Box 4)
  - Atlantic Philanthropic (Box 4)
  - Authorship (Box 4)
  - Automation (Box 4)
  - Automation (Box 4)
  - Automation (Box 4)
  - Automation (Box 4)
  - Automated Info Systems Group (Box 4)
  - Bad Map (Box 4)
  - Baker, Nicholson (Box 4)
  - Bender (Box 4)
  - Bender Room (Box 4)
  - Berger Collection (Box 4)
  - Biblio Citation Databases (Box 4)
  - Bibliographic Instruction (Box 4)
  - Bibliographies, Occasional Publication (Box 4)
  - Binding and Finishing (Box 4)
  - Bing Wing Rededication and Thank You's (Box 4)
  - Bireme (Box 4)
  - Awards Development (Box 4)
  - ARL (Box 4)
  - Bee Lay Tan (Box 4)
  - Berkeley Program Serials List, Shared Cataloging (Box 4)
  - B.J. Williams (Box 4)